"use strict";(self.webpackChunkmcq_practice_app=self.webpackChunkmcq_practice_app||[]).push([[503],{503:e=>{e.exports=JSON.parse('{"name":"Test Practice 1","mcq":[{"question":"Which of the following is the best reason to use a relationship instead of a join?","options":["You are working with multiple tables that you\u2019d like to combine into a single table for analysis","You know that you\u2019d like unmatched values to be dropped from the secondary tables","You wish to avoid data duplication when combining tables with different granularity","You are combining tables based on geographic fields"],"answer":["You wish to avoid data duplication when combining tables with different granularity"],"hasMultipleAnswer":false},{"question":"Relationships are created in which layer?","options":["The data model Layer","The logical layer","The physical layer","The map layer"],"answer":["The logical layer"],"hasMultipleAnswer":false},{"question":"Which of the following is the best reason to create a saved data source as a .TDS file?","options":["Those who wish to use the data do not have access to the underlying data","You want to save the default field properties such as number formats and sort order","You want to save a snapshot of the data that will not update even when the underlying data changes","You need to apply an aggregation that takes too long when using a live connection"],"answer":["You want to save the default field properties such as number formats and sort order"],"hasMultipleAnswer":false},{"question":"When creating a union between tables what will happen if the field names do not match?","options":["Tableau will return an error message explaining that you must modify the tables so that all tables used in the union have the same field names","Tableau will automatically merge the fields combining fields with similar field names","Fields in the union that do not have matching field names will contain null values","Fields with non-matching field names will be dropped so that the union will contain only those fields with matching field names"],"answer":["Fields in the union that do not have matching field names will contain null values"],"hasMultipleAnswer":false},{"question":"In which of the following situations would an outer join be preferred to a blend?","options":["when you need to include all rows from both tables even when the join or blend criteria is not met","when the data is at different level of granularity","when you need to append rows from one table to rows in another table","when the tables are stored in different databases"],"answer":["when you need to include all rows from both tables even when the join or blend criteria is not met"],"hasMultipleAnswer":false},{"question":"Which of the following uses a primary and secondary data source?","options":["Cross-database joins","Unions","Aggregation","Blending"],"answer":["Blending"],"hasMultipleAnswer":false},{"question":"Which of the following can be renamed? [select 3]","options":["Field names","Column values","Parameters","The Measure Names generated field","Sets"],"answer":["Field names","Parameters","Sets"],"hasMultipleAnswer":true},{"question":"Which of the following can have an alias?","options":["Field Names","Values of a continuous measure","Values of a discrete dimensions","Values of a discrete measure","Values of a date field"],"answer":["Values of a discrete dimensions"],"hasMultipleAnswer":false},{"question":"Which of the following are predefined geographic roles? [select two]","options":["Airport","Train terminal","Seaport","Geo code","Zip code"],"answer":["Airport","Zip code"],"hasMultipleAnswer":true},{"question":"Which of the following are default properties which can be assigned to a dimension? [select three]","options":["Shape","Size","Color","Path","Sort"],"answer":["Shape","Color","Sort"],"hasMultipleAnswer":true}]}')}}]);